{
    "subject": "resource/Pythagoras",
    "predicate": "ontology/influenced",
    "object": "resource/Johannes_Kepler",
    "human_readable": "Pythagoras influenced Johannes Kepler.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9648764729499817,
            "question": "What is the historical significance of Pythagoras's influence on Johannes Kepler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9573623538017273,
            "question": "Did Johannes Kepler acknowledge the influence of Pythagoras in his writings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9519524574279785,
            "question": "Were there any specific works by Pythagoras that influenced Johannes Kepler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9478420615196228,
            "question": "What was the impact of Pythagoras on Johannes Kepler's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8800996541976929,
            "question": "Who influenced Johannes Kepler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8168118596076965,
            "question": "To what extent can we attribute Kepler's success to the influence of Pythagoras?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8065164089202881,
            "question": "Can you name any ideas shared between Pythagoras and Johannes Kepler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7214628458023071,
            "question": "How did the ideas of Pythagoras contribute to Kepler's discoveries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6826130151748657,
            "question": "What are some examples of how Pythagoras's legacy lives on through Johannes Kepler's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.634206235408783,
            "question": "How did Pythagoras's teachings potentially shape Kepler's understanding of astronomy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pythagoras influenced Johannes Kepler.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8124_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of how Pythagoras's legacy lives on through Johannes Kepler's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8124_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the ideas of Pythagoras contribute to Kepler's discoveries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8124_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any ideas shared between Pythagoras and Johannes Kepler?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8124_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8124_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8124_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8124_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8124_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8124_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8124_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8124_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8124_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8124_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8124_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Pythagoras had a major impact on scientists such as Nicolaus Copernicus and Johannes Kepler. Additionally, it is stated that Pythagorean ideas influenced thinkers from ancient times up through Kepler in the 17th century, implying a connection between Pythagoras and Kepler's work."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information supporting that Pythagoras had a significant influence on later thinkers, including Johannes Kepler. This is evident from the statements about how Pythagoreanism and its mathematical and philosophical ideas influenced thinkers through history, including Kepler."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}